# SAM KAUFFMAN

hello@samvk.com http://samvk.com 860-878-8669 West Hartford, CT 06107

### **SUMMARY**

An enthusiastic coder who enjoys problem solving and loves bringing others' designs to life. Sam has experience building for the web using the basic front-end technologies HTML(5), CSS(3), and JavaScript(ES7)—amped up with the help of Sass(SCSS) and jQuery. He's in the process of learning more advanced PHP & MySQL to become a better front-end coder and future full-stack developer.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Computer Technician Specialist**

March 2016 – Present

CREC Central, Hartford, CT

- Troubleshooting and resolving issues related to computer hardware as well as printers
- Performing desktop and laptop re-imaging tasks
- Installing software updates and hardware upgrades on end user machines
- Utilizing software such as Remote Desktop and DameWare software to resolve issues remotely

Math Interventionist 2015 – Present

CREC Metropolitan Learning Center, Bloomfield, CT

- Supporting high school students in the strengthening of math skills and conceptual understandings
- Conducting classroom activities based on differentiated learning needs
- Reading and entering school data to track long-term student growth

## Freelance Web Developer

Greater Hartford, CT

2015 - Present

- Performing maintenance and upgrades for existing websites
- Developing mobile-friendly responsive websites
- Basic back-end management with PHP and MySQL
- Technical Skills: HTML(5), CSS(3), Sass(SCSS), & JavaScript(ES7) + iQuery

#### Sales and EasyTech Associate

February – September 2014

Staples Golden Triangle, Lancaster, PA

- Staying current on new technologies
- Resolving computer hardware, software, and operating system issues
- Determining and fulfilling client needs
- Friendly customer service

## **Technical Assistant**

2011 - 2015

F&M Schnader Theatre, Lancaster, PA

- Operating sound board and A/V equipment
- Set construction and rigging
- Loading and unloading set pieces
- Safety checks to assure all set props are secure

• B.A. in Technical Theatre and Design

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Franklin and Marshall College

May 2015

Graduated cum laude